http://www.sitcancer.org/aboutsitc/privacy-policy

This website uses cookies to deliver to you the best experience possible on SITC CONNECT. By continuing to use this site, you are providing to us your consent to ensure you receive such an experience.
View our privacy policy to learn more.
OK
AnnouncementsBlogsCommunitiesDiscussionsEventsGlossarySite ContentLibraries
on this day
between these dates
Posted by
Skip to main content (Press Enter).
Sign in
Skip auxiliary navigation (Press Enter).
Subscribe
Skip main navigation (Press Enter).
Toggle navigation
The Connect Community Create AccountMy ProfileMy CommunitiesMy LibrariesMember DirectoryOpen ForumAbout SITC CONNECTThe Sentinel - SITC BlogEducation & Scientific Exchange SITC Cancer Immunotherapy connectEDAnnual Meeting & Pre-Conference Programs ArchiveSITC17 Webcast Continuing EducationAdvances in Cancer Immunotherapy™ Online 2016 Advances in Cancer Immunotherapy™ Program ArchiveAdvances in Cancer Immunotherapy™ Online 2016 Advances in Cancer Immunotherapy™ Program ArchiveCME/CERegistrationWebcast RegistrationEnduring Materials 20162018 Charleston, SC - 2.242019-2020 Continuing Education Information CME/CE for ASCO 2020 WebinarCME/CE for SITC 2019 WebinarCME/CE for ESMO Immuno Oncology Congress 2019 Webinar2020-2021 Continuing Education InformationRegistrationProgram PurposeWebcast RegistrationEnduring Materials 20162018-2019 Madison, Wis. - 9/6 WebcastMadison, Wis. - 9/6Boston, Mass. - 9/27Indianapolis, Ind. - 10/25Minneapolis, Minn. - TBDNew York City, N.Y. - 11/15Louisville, Ky. - 12/6Pittsburgh, Penn. - 12/15Sacramento, Calif. - 1/10New Orleans, La. - 4/6/19Houston, Texas - 2/9Portland, Ore - 2/21Denver, Co. - TBDSalt Lake City, Utah - TBDToronto, Ont. - TBDSeattle, Wash. - 11/3ACI Planning Committee2019-2020 Charleston, S.C.Boston, Mass.Buffalo, N.Y.Charlotte, N.C.Chicago, Ill.Cleveland, OhioNashville, Tenn.Nashville, Tenn.Philadelphia, Pa.San Diego, Calif.San Francisco, Calif.Tucson, Ariz.SeattleWashington, D.C.TorontoNashville, Tenn. - Webcast2020-2021 San AntonioBostonMadisonPittsburghNew HavenLouisvilleIndianapolisCancer Immunotherapy Winter School Travel Awards Andy Kah Ping Tay, PhDRavi Patel, PhDIzak Faiena, MDJulie Collins, MD, MPHNamrata Chandhok, MDRegistrationSurfaceome WorkshopCytokines in Cancer Immunotherapy Workshop Cytokines in Cancer Immunotherapy Workshop ScheduleRegistration RatesCancer Immune Responsiveness WorkshopAdoptive Cellular Therapies Workshop RegistrationSITC Collaborative Education Programs ArchiveWomen in Cancer Immunotherapy Network 2019 WIN Leadership InstituteWIN Leadership Institute Schedule-ChicagoWIN Leadership Institute Schedule-SeattleSITC Sparkathon Application DetailsMatching Donation ChallengeBusiness CoachesSITC Sparkathon Class of 2017 Projects Team TimIOsThe METIOR Incubator ApplicationThe METIOR Incubator: Checkpoints TeamThe METIOR Incubator: CAR T Cell TeamThe METIOR Incubator MentorsSITC Sparkathon Class of 2018 Projects Team TimIOsThe METIOR Incubator ApplicationThe METIOR Incubator: Checkpoints TeamThe METIOR Incubator: CAR T Cell TeamThe METIOR Incubator MentorsThe METIOR Incubator: CAR T Cell Team2017 Cohort redirectMeet-the-Expert WebinarsCertificate in Cancer Immunotherapy Learner NotificationUpcoming Events SITC Meeting Code of ConductNursing ResourcesResearch Journal for ImmunoTherapy of Cancer New Section DescriptionsSubmit a ManuscriptJITC Editorial BoardJITC Collections COVID-19Immune Checkpoints Beyond PD-1Emerging Immunotherapeutic AgentsMicrobial-Based Cancer ImmunotherapyCancer Immunotherapy GuidelinesImmune Monitoring Technology PrimersMonthly JITC Digest 2018 JITC Digest January 2018JITC Digest February 2018JITC Digest March 2018JITC Digest April 2018JITC Digest May 2018JITC Digest June 2018JITC Digest July 2018JITC Digest August 2018JITC Digest September 2018JITC Digest October 2018JITC Digest November 2018JITC Digest December 20182016 JITC Digest December 20162017 JITC Digest August 2017JITC Digest September 2017JITC Digest October 2017JITC Digest July 2017JITC Digest June 2017JITC Digest May 2017JITC Digest April 2017JITC Digest March 2017JITC Digest February 2017JITC Digest January 20172019 JITC Digest January 2019JITC Digest February 2019JITC Digest March 2019JITC Digest April 2019JITC Digest May 2019JITC Digest June 2019JITC Digest July 2019JITC Digest August 2019JITC Digest September 2019JITC Digest October 2019JITC Digest November 2019JITC Digest December 20192020 JITC Digest January 2020JITC Digest February 2020JITC Digest March 2020JITC Digest April 2020JITC Digest May 2020JITC Digest June 2020JITC Digest July 2020JITC Digest August 2020JITC Digest September 2020JITC Digest October 2020JITC Digest November 2020Editors' Picks Top Articles of 2017JITC's Reading List 2019 FebruaryMarchAprilMayJuneJulyAugustSeptemberOctoberNovemberDecember2020 JanuaryFebruaryMarchMayJuneJulyAugustSeptemberOctoberNovemberSITC Cancer Immunotherapy Guidelines Cutaneous Melanoma Cutaneous Melanoma - Current AlgorithmsGenitourinary Malignancies BladderKidneyProstateHematologic MalignanciesLung CancerOpen Comment PeriodAcute Leukemia SITC Cancer Immunotherapy Guideline – Acute Leukemia Webinar: Continuing Education CreditsHead and NeckCancer Immunotherapy Guideline Webinars: DisclosuresCIG Melanoma Webinar: Continuing Education CreditsCIG Head and Neck Webinar: Continuing Education CreditsCIG RCC Webinar: Continuing Education CreditsCIG Lung Webinar: Continuing Education CreditsCancer Immunotherapy Guideline Webinars: On-DemandMultiple Myeloma CIG Multiple Myeloma Webinar: Continuing Education CreditsLymphoma SITC Cancer Immunotherapy Guideline – Lymphoma Webinar: Continuing Education CreditsImmune-Related Adverse Events Immune Effector Cell-Related Adverse Events GuidelineImmune BiomarkersImmunoscore ValidationImmune ResponsivenessCancer Immunotherapy Principles and Practice TextbookSITC's Guide to Managing Immunotherapy Toxicity TextbookCOVID-19 Resources IL-6 EditorialAdditional COVID-19 ResourcesOpen Access to COVID-19 PublicationsPolicy & Advocacy Policy & Advocacy Archive 201520162017Global Access and ImpactRegulatory IssuesStandards & Quality of CareValue of ImmunotherapyMembership Join/Member BenefitsRenew Your MembershipMembership CategoriesCorporate MembershipMembers OnlyVolunteer Committees Cancer Immunotherapy Guidelines Muliple Myeloma Expert PanelCancer Immunotherapy Guidelines Non-Small Cell Lung Cancer (NSCLC) Expert PanelRegulatory SubcommitteeInternational CommitteeScience and Research SubcommitteeEarly Career ScientistCommunicationsIndustryExecutive CouncilAnnual ProgramChampionsImmune BiomarkersBiomarker Data Sharing SubcommitteeMicrobiome SubcommitteeResources & Useful Tools SubcommitteeTumor Mutational Burden SubcommitteeCancer Immunotherapy Guidelines Renal Cell Carcinoma Expert PanelMembershipQuality SubcommitteeEducation and Training CommitteeAdvances in Cancer Immunotherapy™ (ACI) CommitteeCancer Immunotherapy Guidelines Acute Leukemia Expert PanelPolicy and Advocacy CommitteeBylawsAdvocacy SubcommitteeCancer Immunotherapy Guidelines Oversight CommitteeCancer Immunotherapy Guidelines Lymphoma Expert PanelCancer Immunotherapy Guidelines Melanoma Expert PanelFinance CommitteeCancer Immunotherapy Guidelines Bladder Carcinoma Expert PanelNominating SubcommitteeInternational Young Investigator SubcommitteeCancer Immunotherapy Guidelines Prostate Carcinoma Expert PanelAwards ReviewCancer Immunotherapy Guidelines Head and Neck Expert PanelImmunoscore Steering CommitteeSurgery CommitteeCancer Immunotherapy Guidelines Immune-Checkpoint Inhibitors-Related Adverse EventsCancer Immunotherapy Guidelines Immune Effector Cell (IEC)-related Adverse Events Expert PanelBig Data and Data Sharing CommitteeGlobal Access and Impact CommitteeCancer Immunotherapy Guidelines Breast Expert PanelCancer Immunotherapy Guidelines Hepatocellular Expert PanelCancer Immunotherapy Guidelines Non Melanoma Skin Cancer Expert PanelImmunotherapy Resistance CommitteeImmunoscore Dissemination CommitteePathology CommitteeSITC Task Forces Cancer Immune Responsiveness Task ForceCertification Task ForceBiomarkers Biomarkers Task Force 2009-2012Biomarkers Task Force 2014 - presentImmune Monitoring Technology Primer SeriesPathology Task ForceGenitourinary Malignancies Task ForceImmunoscore Steering Key Information ReleaseCTCAE Task ForceSITC Volunteer Groups World Immunotherapy Council (WIC)Connect-a-ColleaguePath to SITC Leadership2020 SITC Election Padmanee Sharma, MD, PhD • 2020 SITC ElectionLeisha Emens, MD, PhD • 2020 SITC ElectionSandra Demaria, MD • 2020 SITC ElectionTullia Bruno, PhD • 2020 SITC ElectionChristian Capitini, MD • 2020 SITC ElectionKarin Jooss, PhD • 2020 SITC ElectionKimberly Shafer-Weaver, PhD • 2020 SITC ElectionAnn Silk, MD, MS • 2020 SITC ElectionAdekunle Odunsi, MD, PhD, FRCOG, FACOG
• 2020 SITC ElectionJedd Wolchok, MD, PhD • 2020 SITC ElectionFunding 2020 SITC SupportersSupport SITC SOG 2019Faces of the Forward FundFellowships NCI Immunotherapy FellowshipFAQAwards 2014201520162017201820192017 NCI Immunotherapy FellowshipGenentech-KohrtMerck2018 SITC-BMS Translational Fellowship AwardSITC-AstraZeneca ClinicalSITC-Merck Cancer Immunotherapy Clinical Fellowship AwardSITC-SU2C Convergence Scholar Awards SU2C-SITC Convergence Scholar Award 1SU2C-SITC Convergence Scholar Award 2SU2C-SITC Convergence Scholar Award 3SU2C-SITC Convergence Scholar Award 42019 SITC-Amgen Cancer Immunotherapy in Hematologic Malignancies Fellowship AwardSITC-AstraZeneca Immunotherapy in Lung Cancer (Early Stage NSCLC) Clinical Fellowship AwardSITCs Holbrook Kohrt, MD, PhD Cancer Immunotherapy Translational Memorial Fellowship Award2020 SITC-NanoString Technologies Spatial Profiling AwardSITC-BMS Translational Fellowship AwardSITC-Merck Cancer Immunotherapy Clinical FellowshipSITCs Holbrook Kohrt, MD, PhD Cancer Immunotherapy Translational Memorial FellowshipSITC-Amgen Cancer Immunotherapy in Hematologic Malignancies FellowshipSITC-Genentech Women in Cancer Immunotherapy FellowshipSITC-AstraZeneca Immunotherapy in Lung Cancer Clinical FellowshipAwards Richard V. Smalley, MD, Memorial Award and Lectureship Richard V. Smalley Biography20052006200720082009201020112012201320142015201620172018JITC Best Paper Awards 20162015201420172018 Year2019Presidential AwardsYoung Investigator Awards2019 International Scholars2017 International Scholars2015 International ScholarsThe CheckPoints BandCareer Connections Contact Pop-UpAbout SITC Mission & VisionSupport SITC Corporate OpportunitiesPartnershipsHistory of SITC 1986 - 1991: Early Visions1992 - 1998: Finding Our Way1999 - 2006: Growth and Prosperity2007 - 2009: A New EraBoard of Directors SITC Board of DirectorsCareer ConnectionsCommittees, Task Forces and Professional Interest Communities SITC Task ForcesProfessional Interest CommunitiesSITC CommitteesSITC Cancer Immunotherapy Guidelines Expert PanelsMedia Room Cancer Immunotherapy MonthMedia ResourcesImmunotherapy NewsScientific Meeting Highlights from SITC 2017 ESMO 20172016201520142018 2019 AACR Annual Meeting 2019ASCO 2019 Meeting HighlightsESMO Congress 2019 Highlights61st ASH Annual Meeting & Exposition Scientific HighlightsAACR 2018ASCO 2018 Meeting HighlightsASH 2018 Meeting Highlights ASH 2018 Meeting Highlights - Dec. 1ASH 2018 Meeting Highlights - Dec. 2ASH 2018 Meeting Highlights - Dec. 3ASH 2018 Meeting Highlights - Dec. 42020SITC StaffContact SITC
About SITCPrivacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Community Rules, Etiquette and Privacy Guidelines
Last updated: Aug. 3, 2018
Thank you for being part of our community. To ensure the best possible experience for all members, we have established some basic guidelines for participation.
By joining and using this community, you agree that you have read and will follow these rules and guidelines. You also agree to reserve discussions and shared files and content to that are best suited to the medium. This is a great medium with which to solicit the advice of your peers, benefit from their experience, and participate in an ongoing conversation. Questions should be directed to our Membership Department via the Contact Staff link on this site. Technical questions on association management issues should directed to our help desk via email at info@sitcancer.org.
Please take a moment to acquaint yourself with these important guidelines. If you have questions, contact the help desk. In order to preserve a climate that encourages both civil and fruitful dialogue, we reserve the right to suspend or terminate membership in this community for anyone who violate these rules.
The Rules
Do not challenge or attack others. The discussions and comments are meant to stimulate conversation not to create contention. Let others have their say, just as you may.
Do not post commercial messages on any discussion list, resource library entry, or other area where others might see it. Contact people directly with product and service information if you believe it would help them.
Use caution when discussing products. Information posted on the lists and in the libraries is available for all to see, and comments are subject to libel, slander, and antitrust laws.
All defamatory, abusive, profane, threatening, offensive, or illegal materials are strictly prohibited. Do not post anything that you would not want the world to see or that you would not want anyone to know came from you.
Please note carefully all items listed in the disclaimer and legal rules below, particularly regarding the copyright ownership of information posted.
Remember that other participants have the right to reproduce postings to this site unless you specify otherwise.
Post your message or documents only to the most appropriate lists or libraries. Do not spam several lists or libraries with the same message.All messages must add to the body of knowledge. We reserve the right to reject any message for any reason.
Discussion Group Etiquette
Include a signature tag on all messages. Include your name, affiliation, location.
State concisely and clearly the topic of your comments in the subject line. This allows members to respond more appropriately to your posting and makes it easier for members to search the archives by subject.
Include only the relevant portions of the original message in your reply. Delete any header information, and put your response before the original posting.
Only send a message to the entire list when it contains information that everyone can benefit from.
Send messages such as "thanks for the information" or "me, too" to individuals--not to the entire list. Do this by using the "Reply to Sender" link to the left of every message.
Do not send administrative messages, such as remove me from the list. Instead, use the web interface to change your settings or to remove yourself from a list. If you are changing e-mail addresses, you do not need to remove yourself from the list and rejoin under your new e-mail address. Simply change your settings.
Warn other list subscribers of lengthy messages either in the subject line or at the beginning of the message body with a line that says "Long Message."
Do not publicize employment opportunities/job postings on a SITC CONNECT community. If you are looking to advertise an open position, please visit the SITC Job Board or contact SITC at info@sitcancer.org for more information regarding how to do this.
The Legal Stuff
This site is provided as a service for the members of Society for Immunotherapy of Cancer.  Society for Immunotherapy of Cancer is not responsible for the opinions and information posted on this site by others. We disclaim all warranties with regard to information posted on this site, whether posted by Society for Immunotherapy of Cancer or any third party; this disclaimer includes all implied warranties of merchantability and fitness. In no event shall Society for Immunotherapy of Cancer be liable for any special, indirect, or consequential damages or any damages whatsoever resulting from loss of use, data, or profits, arising out of or in connection with the use or performance of any information posted on this site.
Do not post any defamatory, abusive, profane, threatening, offensive, or illegal materials. Do not post any information or other material protected by copyright without the permission of the copyright owner. By posting material, the posting party warrants and represents that he or she owns the copyright with respect to such material or has received permission from the copyright owner. In addition, the posting party grants Society for Immunotherapy of Cancer and users of this site the nonexclusive right and license to display, copy, publish, distribute, transmit, print, and use such information or other material.
Messages should not be posted if they encourage or facilitate members to arrive at any agreement that either expressly or impliedly leads to price fixing, a boycott of another's business, or other conduct intended to illegally restrict free trade. Messages that encourage or facilitate an agreement about the following subjects are inappropriate: prices, discounts, or terms or conditions of sale; salaries; profits, profit margins, or cost data; market shares, sales territories, or markets; allocation of customers or territories; or selection, rejection, or termination of customers or suppliers.
Society for Immunotherapy of Cancer does not actively monitor the site for inappropriate postings and does not on its own undertake editorial control of postings. However, in the event that any inappropriate posting is brought to the attention of Society for Immunotherapy of Cancer we will take all appropriate action.
Society for Immunotherapy of Cancer reserves the right to terminate access to any user who does not abide by these guidelines.Privacy Policy
WE RESPECT YOUR PRIVACY
Any personal information you provide to us including and similar to your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address will not be released, sold, or rented to any entities or individuals outside of our organization except as noted below.
WITH WHOM DO WE SHARE THE PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT THROUGH THIS SITE
Our Service Providers. We may share your personal information with companies (including our affiliates) that perform services on our behalf, for example, companies that help process credit card payments. Our service providers are required by contract to protect the confidentiality of the personal information we share with them and to use it only to provide specific services on our behalf. Business Transfers. Your personal information may be transferred to another entity (either an affiliated entity or an unrelated third party) in connection with a merger, reorganization, dissolution or similar corporate event. If such a transfer were ever to occur, the acquiring entity’s use of your personal information will still be subject to this Privacy Policy. Government and Legal Disclosures We may disclose the personal information we collect through this Site, when we, in good faith, believe disclosure is appropriate to comply with the law (or a court order or subpoena); to prevent or investigate a possible crime, such as fraud or identity theft; to enforce our Terms and Conditions or other agreements that govern your use of this Site; or to protect the rights, property or safety of our company, our users, or others.
EXTERNAL SITES.
We are not responsible for the content of external internet sites. You are advised to read the privacy policy of external sites before disclosing any personal information.
Information Collected Automatically
AUTOMATED INFORMATION
Your web browser or mobile device automatically provides information when you visit the Site, including, but not limited to, your Internet Protocol (IP) address or unique device identifier.
EMAIL INTERCONNECTIVITY
If you receive email communications from us, we may use certain tools to capture data related to when you open our messages, click on hyperlinks or banners it may contain and make purchases. We use this information to enhance and support our marketing and sales operations.
MAILING LISTS
When you sign up for one of our mailing lists, newsletters or a marketing list, we collect your email address and postal address. Users may opt out of receiving future communications at any time by visiting the SITC Email Subscription Management webpage on SITC CONNECT.
LOG FILES
Log files store information such as a user’s IP address, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks. Like most websites, the Site uses log files to analyze trends, administer the Site, and track users’ movement on the Site.
UPDATING USER PROFILE
Individuals who have created an account on SITC CONNECT have the ability to update or change all personal information provided. To do so, please visit your My Profilepage, when logged in, to edit the information available. To control what users can see on your profile, visit your Privacy Settings, located underneath the My Account tab of your profile page.
ABC provides individuals the opportunity to opt out of receiving communications from us when we request information about the user. To update these preferences, please visit the SITC Email Subscription Management webpage on SITC CONNECT.
Google AdWords
This Site uses the Google AdWords remarketing service to advertise on third-party websites (including Google) to previous visitors to the Site. We may advertise to previous visitors who have not completed a task on the Site, for example, using the contact form to make an inquiry. The task may appear the form of an advertisement on the Google search results page or a site in the Google Display Network. Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on users’ past visits to the Site. Any data collected will be used in accordance with this privacy policy and Google’s privacy policy. Users may opt out of this service through the Google Ads Settings or Google Ad Settings mobile resource.
COOKIES
A "cookie" is a small data text file that is placed in your browser and allows us to recognize you each time you visit this site (personalization, etc). Cookies are used to provide smoother navigation throughout the Site, such as to store a saved password; to identify user trends, such as page views; and for other internal purposes, such as to assess the effectiveness of the Site. You have the option of setting your computer to disable cookies or to alert you when cookies are being used. If you choose to disable cookies, please be aware that portions of the Site may not function properly
REMEMBER THE RISKS WHENEVER YOU USE THE INTERNET
While we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to us and you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any passwords or other account information. In addition other Internet sites or services that may be accessible through our site have separate data and privacy practices independent of us, and therefore we disclaim any responsibility or liability for their policies or actions. Please contact those vendors and others directly if you have any questions about their privacy policies. For any other information please contact us using the Contact Us page.
Membership Links
Join
Renew
Member Directory
My ProfileGet Involved
Email Sign-up
Volunteer
Support SITC
© 2020 Society for Immunotherapy of Cancer (SITC). All rights reserved. Privacy Policy.
555 East Wells Street, Suite 1100 | Milwaukee, WI | 53202-3823 | USA Tel: +1 414 271 2456 | Fax: +1 414 276 3349 | Email: info@sitcancer.org
Powered by Higher Logic
